The Northern Wasteland army is attacking.
General,
what should we do?
Send word to the court
and the general immediately
to report the crisis at Immortal Pass.
Yes, sir.
Daxi and the Northern Wasteland
has agreed to peace talks.
Why have you broken your promise
and gone back on your word?
A nobody like you
is not worthy to speak with me.
The agreement was made with Wu Jie.
Now that he's gone,
the agreement naturally becomes void!
The general hasn't returned,
and we haven't received the order.
What are we going to do?
Behind the Immortal Pass
lies the heartland of Daxi.
Our fathers, mothers,
and loved ones are there.
Even if we die,
we cannot let the Northern Wastelanders
through the pass.
We must hold the gates at all costs.
Defend! Defend! Defend!
Attack!
Kill!
Where is General Wu?
He's still fine for now.
But who knows for how much longer?
Qiushui.
The moment
you stepped into this camp,
you've sent him to his grave.
Don't you think you're so capable,
wanting to be a hero
who saves the country and its people?
Today, I'll tell you...
You won't accomplish anything.
Where is General Wu?
Do you think you can beat me?
Winning or losing doesn't matter.
Tell me where General Wu is.
Why the rush?
We don't have much time left
for General Wu.
If you defeat me,
I'll tell you.
General! General! General!
Terrible news!
Ambushers are attacking the inner city!
General!
General,
the city gates have been breached!
Fall back to defend the inner city!
Kill!
Xiao Kaiyan.
It's time to end things for you.
Another stroke of luck?
You think you've won.
Xiao Qiushui.
You want to save General Wu,
but I refuse to tell you.
What can you do about it?
Hand over General Wu.
Kaiyan.
Father?
Father.
Kaiyan,
among my three children,
you are the most reliable.
Since Huanhua has you,
I can rest easy.
Father.
Kaiyan,
why are you back so late?
Are you hungry?
What would you like to eat?
I'll make it for you right away.
Mother!
Mother, Yiren!
Kaiyan,
I got you a good sword.
Come take a look!
Kaiyan.
Kaiyan,
we agreed to venture
into the martial world together.
Let's go now.
Xiao Qiushui!
You took shortcuts,
absorbing others' energy,
which led you astray
and killed so many innocent people.
When there is no self in one's heart,
only then can you understand
heaven and earth.
By showing compassion for others,
only then can you connect with
all living beings.
You've only ever seen yourself
in your eyes.
How could you possibly understand
that the highest state of Voidheart
is actually compassion?
Qiushui.
I see...
it's snowing.
Second Brother.
This is the last time I'll call you that.
I'm the only one left in the Xiao family.
I will now make amends
for the mistakes you made.
Tell me
where General Wu is.
where General Wu is!
General Wu...
Is...
The outcome is decided.
Immortal Pass
already belongs to the Northern Wasteland.
Your desperate struggle
will only lead to death.
We swear to defend Daxi to the death,
unwavering in our commitment!
-Unwavering commitment!
You're nothing but
Wu Jie's remnant forces.
Damn Northern Wastelanders,
get out of Daxi!
-Get out of Daxi!
Foolish commoners blind to the times,
even Daxi's emperor
is willing to cede territory
for temporary peace!
Will anyone come to save you?
Move aside or I'll kill you all.
I, Liang Dou, have brought
Daxi's martial world
to guard the nation's gate.
I'd like to see
whether Daxi's martial world is formidable
or if the Northern Wasteland's experts
are more superior.
Attack!
Qiushui.
General!
It's the General!
All soldiers, hear my command!
-Yes, sir!
Follow me
and fight our way out of the city!
Charge!
Guards,
summon Li Chenzhou.
Tell him to rescue
General Wu at all costs!
Your Majesty!
Great victory!
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
victory at Immortal Pass!
in the battle at Immortal Pass,
Wu Jie defeated
the Northern Wasteland Army!
The Northern Wasteland Army's general,
Helian Yan, was beheaded.
The Northern Wasteland has surrendered
and promised not to invade
the Central Plains for 50 years!
Good.
Very good!
Issue the order:
Reward Wu Jie
and the frontline soldiers generously.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Wait.
And Chenzhou
should be rewarded too.
Your Majesty,
Chief Li has already...
While searching for General Wu,
he died.
What did you say?
Chenzhou...
Thank you, Mr. Xiao.
General Wu.
The Xiao family honors promises.
You risked your life to save me.
I will never forget
this debt of gratitude.
Come.
Drink!
Let me drink first to show my respect!
Come, I'll join you.
Good wine!
Wu Army!
Here!
Mr. Xiao,
on behalf of the entire Wu Army,
I toast to
your Shenzhou Sworn Brotherhood!
Cheers!
-Cheers!
Bottoms up!
Cheers!
Thank you, Mr. Xiao.
Such good wine!
Let's drink till we drop.
Cheers!
Come!
Brothers.
This cup
is to all our brothers
who died fighting the Northern Wasteland.
Today's victory
is partly theirs as well.
This one...
Let's drink to ourselves.
To ourselves!
-Good!
-Drink!
To ourselves!
Come!
- Go.
Let's go drink over there.
Let's drink with those guys.
Let's go.
I'm telling you all,
we're no longer the Four Thugs.
We're now the Five Thugs...
Five, Six Thugs now!
We were like this and then like that.
Drink!
No one leaves sober!
Come on, drink up!
Come on, have a drink!
Here, pour some more.
Come on.
Good.
Great tolerance!
Here, like this, and again.
Tang Fang.
Qiushui.
Knowing you
is the greatest joy of my life.
Your family master
doesn't allow women to marry out.
Then can you have a husband marry in?
Well...
A live-in son-in-law?
Big Brother, Second, Fourth Brothers,
come here quick.
Zuoqiu is going to be
a live-in son-in-law!
Zuoqiu is marrying into the Qu family!
Will their children
have to take the Qu surname?
That's fine.
What's wrong with the Qu surname?
I'm not jealous at all.
We have Fifth Thug.
We'll live together
with Fifth Thug from now on.
Right, we'll live with Fifth Thug.
Won't that make us five bachelors?
Five bachelors it is then.
Fourth Brother,
you're not stuttering anymore.
You're right.
Come on, drink more.
Big Brother.
Miss Tang.
Let's enjoy the wine while we can.
Let me toast you two.
This feels great.
Who says our Fifth Thug must be bachelors?
I'm not.
Everything for Daxi.
Each of them
is a great hero of Daxi.
Qiushui!
Miss Tang.
I'd like to toast you two.
May you enjoy your drinks!
I'll drink up.
Qiushui,
on such a wonderful day,
let's sing a song together!
Alright!
Brothers.
Let's sing together now.
Time to sing.
You start first.
-You start.
-Sure!
Xiao Qiushui,
you've won.
The martial world,
at the end of the day,
is united by righteousness.
I see a different martial world too.
Xiao Qiushui.
We'll meet
when fate brings us together again.
Qiushui knew well
that using the Voidheart Codex
at the 15th level
would have consequences.
Although it could unleash
power several times
beyond his own strength,
making him temporarily invincible,
it would drain
his vital energy completely,
damaging his meridians
and depleting his life force soon after.
He paid with his life!
Mingming, after thorough investigation,
we've confirmed
Li Nan's espionage activities.
He was acting under orders
from a foreign spy organization
to steal state secrets.
Unfortunately,
before he could be sentenced,
he died two days ago.